(Sheldon:)Why do we have a geology book?
(Sheldon:)Leonard, did you throw
a children's party
(Sheldon:)while I was in Texas?
(Penny:)Wait. What's wrong with geology?
(Sheldon:)Let me put this in a way
you'll understand, Penny.
(Sheldon:)You remember
how you explained to me
(Sheldon:)that the Kardashians
aren't real celebrities?
(Sheldon:)Well, geology
is the Kardashians of science.
(Sheldon:)Have you considered
studying standard model physics?
(Penny:)You want me
to give up string theory
(Sheldon:)for something
that's less advanced?
(Sheldon:)You know, why don't you break up
with Penny
(Sheldon:)and start dating a brown bear.
(Penny:)Like you could
get a brown bear.
(Leonard:)Hey, I've got a good job.
(Leonard:)I could buy salmon.
You don't know.
(Amy:)Maybe you could make
your new field of study
(Amy:)the calculation
of nuclear matrix elements.
(Sheldon:)Oh, please.
(Sheldon:)If I wanted to take up a fad,
I'd get a tramp stamp.
(Leonard:)What about loop quantum gravity?
Oh, Duchess, look at me!